On side effects of having it all, I got to talk to Tabitha, I feel like in a much more homey kind of way than I feel like I've seen other interviewers approach.
And I think that's a testament to her deciding that this was a safe space where she could be like that.
Right. She told us a story that she hadn't put in her book.
She told us about, you know, just not only her gift, but just how illness actually brought her to her gift.
And I think that was something that a lot of people could relate to just in the realizing that like your body is speaking to you in ways that you just don't understand until you allow yourself to understand.
Like it started with a headache in the back of my head. That headache stayed there for a year and seven months every day. Never went away.
Some days were better than others. Right. But some days I couldn't walk. It was just a crazy time for me.
I got to a place where I was like, OK, Lord, I'm gonna try one more time and I'm gonna beg and I'm gonna plead with you.
And I was like, God, if you heal me, you can have me. And I meant it.
And it was the first time I'd ever. What did that mean?
It meant I'm not gonna try to live my life my way anymore. I'm gonna live it how you created me to live it.